Guide to the Rice University athletic records, 1912-2010 (UA 155) UA 155
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Film and Video by Sport, 1937-2006 (Boxes 101-154), 198865
  - Men's Basketball 1999, 199204 (Box 138)
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Air Force Tape 2 (2 copies), 199235
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at Tulsa Tape 1, 199234
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at Tulsa Tape 2, 199233
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at Navy Tape 1, 199232
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at Navy Tape 2, 199231
    - 11.19.99 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Navy Tape 3, 199230
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. UNLU Tape 1, 199229
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at UNLU Tape 2, 199228
    - Rice Men's Basketball at ISU Tournament vs. St. Mary's Tape 2, 199227
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at ISU Tourney vs. ISU Tape 1, 199226
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at ISU Tourney vs. ISU Tape 2, 199225
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Wyoming Tape 2, 199224
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. UNLV Tape 2, 199223
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at San Fran Tourney vs. Holy Cross Tape 1, 199222
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. TCU Tape 1, 199221
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at UNLV Highlights Tape 1, 199220
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at San Fran Tourney vs. Weber State Tape 2, 199219
    - 2.25.99 Rice Men's Basketball at TCU Tape 2, 199218
    - 12.20.99 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Rockhurst College Tape 2, 199217
    - 12.28.99 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Duquesne Tape 3, 199216
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at SMU Tape 1, 199215
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. Louisiana College Tape 2, 199214
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. SMU Overtime Tape, 199213
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at SMU Tape 2, 199212
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. CSU Tape 1, 199211
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. CSU Tape 2, 199210
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. SMU Tape 1 followed by overtime period, 199209
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball vs. SMU Tape 2, 199208
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at San Fran Tourney vs. Weber State Tape 1, 199207
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at Wyoming Tape 1, 199206
    - 1999 Rice Men's Basketball at Wyoming Tape 2, 199205
  - Men's Basketball 1999-2000, 199160 (Box 139)
    - 11.21.00 Rice vs. U Houston VHS, 199203
    - 12.4.00 Rice vs. Middletown St Tape 1, 199202
    - 12.4.00 Rice vs. Middletown St Tape 3, 199201
    - 11.18.00 Rice vs. Navy Tape 1, 199200
    - 11.18.00 Rice vs. Navy Tape 2, 199199
    - 12.20.00 Rice vs. Port St Tape 1, 199198
    - 12.20.00 Rice vs. Port St Tape 2, 199197
    - 11.24.00 Rice vs. Birmingham S. Tape 1, 199196
    - 11.24.00 Rice vs. Birmingham S. Tape 2, 199195
    - 12.2.00 Rice vs. Lamar Tape 1, 199194
    - 12.2.00 Rice vs. Lamar Tape 2, 199193
    - 11.9.00 Men's Basketball Exhibition Tape 1, 199192
    - 11.9.00 Men's Basketball Exhibition Tape 3, 199191
    - 11.13.00 Men's Basketball Exhibition Tape 1, 199190
    - 12.20.00 Port St, 199189
    - 11.28.00 Stephen F. VHS, 199188
    - 11.21.00 Houston VHS, 199187
    - 12.28.00 Rice vs. Baylor VHS, 199186
    - 12.9.00 Rice vs. BYU Tape 2 (Compaq), 199185
    - 1999 Rice vs. Wyoming Tape 1, 199184
    - 1999 Rice vs. Missouri-Rolla Tape 3, 199183
    - 12.11.99 Rice vs. Texas A and MTape 1, 199182
    - 3.2.99 Rice vs. San Jose St VHS, 199181
    - 1.8.99 Rice at SMU, 199180
    - 1.16.99 Rice vs. Air Force, 199179
    - 3.4.99 Rice vs. New Mexico, 199178
    - 1.16.99 Rice vs. Air Force, 199177
    - 12.2.99 Rice vs. Northwestern St. Tape 1, 199176
    - 12.4.99 Rice vs. SFASU Tape 2, 199175
    - 1999 Rice vs. SF Austin Tape 1, 199174
    - 1999 Rice vs. Stephen F. Austin Tape 2, 199173
    - 1999 Rice at WAC Tourn vs. SJS Tape 1, 199172
    - 12.4.00 Middletown VHS, 199171
    - 1999 Rice vs. Mississippi Tape 2, 199170
    - 12.20.99 Rice vs. Rockhurst College Tape 1, 199169
    - 1999 Rice vs. Portland Tape 2, 199168
    - 1999 Rice vs. University of Houston Tape 1, 199167
    - 1999 Rice vs. Portland Tape 1, 199166
    - 1999 Rice at WAC Tourn vs. New Mexico Tape 1, 199165
    - 2.9.99 Rice at CSU Tape 1, 199164
    - 1998-99 Rice vs. UT Pan-American Tape 1, 199163
    - 12.2.99 Rice vs. Northwestern St. Tape 2-, 199162
    - 1999 Rice at San Fran Tourney vs. Holy Cross Tape 2, 199161
  - Men's Basketball 2000-2001, 199119 (Box 140)
    - 1.16.00 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 2, 199159
    - 1.13.01 Rice vs. Siena VHS, 199158
    - 12.30.01 Duquesne VHS, 199157
    - 2.8.01 TU, 199156
    - 11.21.00 Rice vs. Houston Tape 1, 199155
    - 11.21.00 Rice vs. Houston Tape 2, 199154
    - 12.4.00 Rice vs. Middletown St. Tape 2, 199153
    - 2.14.00 Rice at Tulsa Tape 1, 199152
    - 11.24.00 San Diego- Hawaii VHS, 199151
    - 2.19.00 Hawaii Hilites VHS, 199150
    - 3.8.01 Fresno St. vs. Rice VHS, 199149
    - 1.20.01 Hawaii vs. San Jose State VHS, 199148
    - 3.15.01 Hawaii vs. SMU VHS, 199147
    - 2.1.01 Hawaii vs. Fresno VHS, 199146
    - 2.7.00 Rice vs. SMU Tape 2, 199145
    - 1.18.01 SMU vs. Rice VHS, 199144
    - 12.2.00 Rice-Lamar, 199143
    - 11.28.00 Stephen F. Austin VHS, 199142
    - 2000-2001 Men's Basketball Highlights (2 copies, VHS), 199141
    - 2.19.01 Rice at Hawaii (2 copies VHS), 199140
    - 1.20.01 Rice at TCU (2 copies VHS), 199139
    - 12.30.00 Rice vs. Duquesne Tape 1, 199138
    - 12.30.00 Rice vs. Duquesne Tape 2, 199137
    - 1.8.00 Rice at SMU Tape 1, 199136
    - 2000-2001 Western Athletic Conference, 199135
    - 1.29.00 Rice vs. UTEP Tape 2, 199134
    - 12.9.00 Rice vs. BYU Tape 1 compaq, 199133
    - 2.9.00 Rice vs. Hawaii Tape 2, 199132
    - 2000 Rice vs. Hawaii Half #2, 199131
    - 2.26.00 Rice vs. Fresno St. Tape 1, 199130
    - 2000 Rice vs. Hawaii Half #1, 199129
    - 11.9.00 Men's Basketball Exhibition beta, 199128
    - 11.13.00 Men's Basketball Exhibition Tape 2 beta, 199127
    - 2.17.00 Rice vs. SJSU Tape 1, 199126
    - 1.03.00 Rice vs. UTPA Tape 1, 199125
    - 1.03.00 Rice vs. UTPA Tape 2, 199124
    - 11.28.00 Rice vs. SF Austin Tape 1, 199123
    - 11.28.00 Rice vs. SF Austin Tape 2, 199122
    - 12.28.00 Rice vs. Baylor Tape 1, 199121
    - 12.28.00 Rice vs. Baylor Tape 2, 199120
  - Men's Basketball 2001-2002, 199074 (Box 141)
    - 1.25.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Tape 1, 199118
    - 1.25.01 Rice vs. Hawaii Tape 2, 199117
    - 3.1.01 Rice vs. Fresno St. Tape 1, 199116
    - 2.5.01 Rice vs. SMU Tape 1, 199115
    - 2.5.01 Rice vs. SMU Tape 2, 199114
    - 2001 Rice vs. SMU Tape 1, 199113
    - 2001 Rice vs. SMU Tape 2, 199112
    - 2001 Rice vs. TCU Tape 1, 199111
    - 2001 Rice vs. TCU Tape 2, 199110
    - 2.10.01 Rice vs. TCU Tape 1, 199109
    - 2.10.01 Rice vs. TCU Tape 2, 199108
    - 2.22.01 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 1, 199107
    - 2.22.01 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 2, 199106
    - 2.8.01 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 1, 199105
    - 2.8.01 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 2, 199104
    - 2.28.02 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 1, 199103
    - 2.14.02 Rice vs. La Tech Tape 1, 199102
    - 2.14.02 Rice vs. La Tech Tape 2, 199101
    - 2001 Rice vs. Nevada at Wac Tape 1, 199100
    - 2001 Rice vs. Nevada at Wac Tape 2, 199099
    - 1.6.01 Rice vs. Nevada Tape 1, 199098
    - 1.6.01 Rice vs. Nevada Tape 2, 199097
    - 1.5.02 Nevada vs. Rice VHS, 199096
    - 1.31.02 Rice vs. Nevada Tape 2, 199095
    - 3.03.01 Rice vs. Nevada Tape 1, 199094
    - 3.03.01 Rice vs. Nevada Tape 2, 199093
    - 2000-2001 Rice Men's Basketball Video Mugs, 199092
    - 2.24.01 Rice vs. Utep Tape 1, 199091
    - 2.24.01 Rice vs. Utep Tape 2, 199090
    - 2.24.01 Rice vs. Utep Tape 3, 199089
    - 1.13.01 Rice vs. Sienna Tape 1, 199088
    - 1.13.01 Rice vs. Sienna Tape 2, 199087
    - 2.1.01 Rice vs. UTEP Tape 1, 199086
    - 2.1.01 Rice vs. UTEP Tape 2, 199085
    - 2001 Rice vs. FSU at Wac Tape 1 VHS, 199084
    - 2001 Rice vs. FSU at Wac Tape 2 VHS, 199083
    - 12.7.02 ISU vs. Binghamton VHS, 199082
    - 11.30.02 Rice at Brigham Young University 2 copies VHS, 199081
    - 1.10.01 Rice vs. UT Pan Am, 199080
    - 1.4.01 Rice vs. Fresno State Tape 1, 199079
    - 1.4.01 Rice vs. Fresno State Tape 2, 199078
    - 3.1.01 Rice vs. Fresno State Tape 2, 199077
    - 1.27.01 Rice vs. SJS Tape 1, 199076
    - 1.27.01 Rice vs. SJS Tape 2, 199075
  - Men's Basketball 2002-2004, 199029 (Box 142)
    - 1.25.03 Rice vs. La Tech Tape 1, 199073
    - 1.25.03 Rice vs. La Tech Tape 2, 199072
    - 2.20.03 Rice at La Tech VHS, 199071
    - 2.20.03 La Tech vs. Rice VHS, 199070
    - 2003-2004 Rice vs. Houston VHS, 199069
    - 2004 Rice vs. Houston Tape 1, 199068
    - 2004 Rice vs. Houston Tape 2, 199067
    - 2004 Basketball Mugs, 199066
    - 2004 Raw Willis Wilson Footage 5 min, 199065
    - 2003 Halloween Hoops, 199064
    - 11.7.03 Men's Basketball Jersey Retirement Pass Conf, 199063
    - 11.30.01 Rice vs. Stanford (3 copies - including on DVD), 199062
    - 1.2.04 Rice vs. UConn Tape 2 (including DVD copy), 199061
    - 1.2.04 Rice vs. UConn Tape 3 (including DVD copy), 199060
    - 1.31.04 Rice vs. SJS 1st half, 199059
    - 1.31.04 Rice vs. SJS 2nd half, 199058
    - 2.27.03 Rice vs. SJS, 199057
    - 2.8.03 Rice at Tulsa VHS, 199056
    - 2.8.03 TU vs. Rice VHS, 199055
    - 2.14.04 Rice vs. Tulsa, 199054
    - 1.23.03 Rice vs. SMU Tape 1, 199053
    - 1.23.03 Rice vs. SMU Tape 2, 199052
    - 1.20.04 Rice vs. SMU Tape 1, 199051
    - 2.24.03 Rice at SMU VHS, 199050
    - - 2.22.03 SMU vs. Rice VHS, 199049
    - 1.23.03 SMU at Rice VHS, 199048
      Contents include: a mpg master file of the Rice v. SMU game and an access copy mp4.
    - 2.23.02 University of Hawaii vs. Rice VHS, 199047
    - Men's WAC Hawaii vs. Rice, 2003; 199046
      Contents include: a mpg master file of the WAC Hawaii v. Rice game and an mp4 access copy.
    - 3.13.03 Rice vs. Hawaii at WAC Tourney Tape 1 (including DVD copy), 199045
    - 3.13.03 Rice vs. Hawaii at WAC Tourney Tape 2 (including DVD copy), 199044
    - Rice vs. Hawaii, 199043
    - 1.28.04 Rice vs. Hawaii Tape 1, 199042
    - 1.28.04 Rice vs. Hawaii Tape 2, 199041
    - 1.28.04 Rice vs. Hawaii Tape 3, 199040
    - 2.1.03 Rice, 199039
    - 2.27.03 San Jose at Rice VHS, 199038
    - 2003 Rice vs. Idaho St. Top of the World VHS, 199037
    - 2002-2003 Rice Men's Basketball VHS, 199036
    - 12.30.02 Louisiana College at Rice (2 copies) VHS, 199035
    - 2002-2003 Rice Owl Playbook VHS, 199034
    - 12.7.02 Lamar at Rice VHS, 199033
    - Lamar vs. Rice VHS, 2003-12-18; 199032
      Content includes: a master mpg of Lamar v. Rice and an access copy mp4.
    - 1.16.03 Rice at Boise State VHS, 199031
    - 3.8.03 Rice vs. FSU (2 betas) VHS (including DVD copy), 199030
  - Men's Basketball 2004-2005, 198989 (Box 143)
    - 3.3.05 Rice vs. LA Tech (including DVD copy), 199028
    - Rice vs. SMU (including DVD copy), 2005-03-05; 199027
    - 1.31.04 Rice vs. San Jose, 199026
    - 1.29.05 San Jose State University, 199025
    - 1.22.04 Fresno St vs. Rice, 199024
    - 2.23.04 Rice vs. Fresno St (2 copies VHS), 199023
    - 2.21.05 Rice at Fresno St, 199022
    - 2.14.04 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 1, 199021
    - 2.14.04 Rice vs. Tulsa Tape 3, 199020
    - 1.17.04 Rice vs. TU, 199019
    - ESPN College Bball – Rice vs. Tulsa, 2004-01-17; 199018
      Contents include: a mpg master file of the Rice v. Tulsa game and an mp4 access copy.
    - 1.8.04 Rice vs. Boise St, 199017
    - 1.8.05 Boise St. vs. Rice, 199016
    - 2.7.04 Boise St. vs. Rice, 199015
    - 12.16.04 Lamar Cardinals vs. Rice Owls, 199014
    - 3.17.04 Rice at University of Wisconsin at Milwaukee; Eli Roe, Jon Goble, Billy Dunlap, 199013
    - 2.27.04 Rice, 199012
    - 11.26.05 Men's Basketball Ducks vs. Rice, 199011
    - 1.2.04 Rice vs. UConn Tape 1, 199010
    - 2005 Rice vs. BSU, 199009
    - 2005 Rice vs. FSU (2 copies beta), 199008
    - Rice vs. ULL ESPN Bracketbuster, 2004-02-21; 199007
      Contents include: a mpg master file of the Rice v. ULL game and an access mp4.
    - 11.27.04 Rice at Louisiana – Lafayette, 199006
    - 2.21.04 Rice vs. Louisiana – Lafayette 1st half only, 199005
    - 3.5.05 Rice at SMU, 199004
    - 2.7.04 Stanford, 199003
    - 2.8.05 Rockhurst, 199002
    - 2.05.04 Utep vs. Rice (4 copies), 199001
    - 2005 Rice vs. Utep, 199000
    - 1.28.04 Rice vs. Hawaii, 198999
    - 3.11.04 Rice vs. Hawaii, 198998
    - 1.22.04 Hawaii vs. UTEP, 198997
    - 2.27.05 Rice vs. Hawaii (1 beta, 1 VHS, 1 DVD), 198996
    - 2.18.04 Rice vs. Nevada, 198995
    - 1.24.04 Rice at Nevada, 198994
    - 1.22.05 Rice vs. Nevada, 198993
    - 2.18.04 Rice vs. Nevada Tape 1, 198992
    - 2.18.04 Rice vs. Nevada Tape 2, 198991
    - 2.16.05 Rice vs. Nevada, 198990
  - Men's Basketball 2005-2006 and undated, 198957 (Box 144)
    Formats: Beta, CD, VHS
    - Tulsa and SMU, 198988
    - Rice vs. Tulsa (2 VHS), 198987
    - Rice vs. Houston, 198986
    - UH vs. Rice, 198985
    - Rice at SMU, 198984
    - Rice vs. SMU, 198983
    - Rice at SMU, 198982
    - 3.8.06 Rice vs. SMU CUSA, 198981
    - 3.8.06 Rice vs. SMU CUSA Game 1, 198980
    - Rice vs. SMU 1st, 198979
    - Rice vs. SMU 2nd, 198978
    - Rice vs. UTEP 1st half, 198977
    - Rice vs. UTEP 2nd half, 198976
    - 2.18.06 Rice vs. UTEP, 198975
    - Rice vs. Lamar, 198974
    - Rice vs. PN, 198973
    - Rice vs. Texas SWC, 198972
    - HBU 1, 198971
    - HBU 2, 198970
    - Fresno at Rice, 198969
    - Rice vs. Fresno, 198968
    - BYU, 198967
    - Rice vs. BYU; Melanie at the end, 198966
    - Utah at Rice, 198965
    - Rice vs. Ind. St, 198964
    - Rice at Kansas, 198963
    - Iowa State Bball vs. Rice, 198962
    - Rice at Iowa, 198961
    - Rice at Texas, 198960
    - Rice vs. FSU, 198959
    - Rice at NM, 198958
  - Women's Basketball 1993-2003, 198956 (Box 145)
  - Women's Basketball 2003-2005, 198955 (Box 146)
  - Track 1985-2005 and undated, 198917 (Box 147)
    - 9.1.04 XC, 198954
    - 3.29.03 Outdoor Track, 198953
    - 3.29.05 Track, 198952
    - 4.2.05 Track, 198951
    - 3.31.01 W Track, 198950
    - 9.16.00 XC, 198949
    - 8.29.03 XC at UH, 198948
    - 1.23.04 Track at UH Tape 1, 198947
    - 1.23.04 Track at UH Tape 2, 198946
    - 1.27.01 Rice M and W Track at UH Indoor, 198945
    - 1.23.04 Track at UH, 198944
    - 9.14.02 Rice XC (2 COPIES), 198943
    - 1.25.03 Rice Indoor Track (2 copies), 198942
    - 8.14.02 Rice XC, 198941
    - 3.30.02 Track Top #2, 198940
    - 2.5.05 Indoor Track, 198939
    - 1997 NCAA DI Men's and Women's Indoor Track Championships Women's 4x 400 Relay, 198938
    - 3.8.02 Rice Track NCAA Championships, 198937
    - 1990 blank (VHS), 198936
    - 1990 NCAA Indoor TV, 198935
    - 1991 Indoor Conference, 198934
    - 1992 Texas Relays (2 copies), 198933
    - 1992 Indoor Conference, 198932
    - 1992 SWC Outdoor ESPN, 198931
    - 1.29.93 Sooner Indoor/2.6.93 LSU, 198930
    - 1993 Conference Outdoor, 198929
    - 1993 Outdoor at Rice Institute, 198928
    - 2.13.93 Oklahoma Classic Indoor, 198927
    - 1.29.94 Oklahoma Indoor, 198926
    - 2.11.94-2.12.94 Oklahoma Classic, 198925
    - 1994 Conference Outdoor, 198924
    - 1996 CC Video, 198923
    - 1997 4X400 Women's Indoor Rice Nat. Champs, 198922
    - 1997 Women's 4X400, 198921
    - 1985 NCAA Indoor, 198920
    - 1985 NCAA Indoor Championships, 198919
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color film produced by ESPN of the NCAA Indoor Championships held at the Carrier Dome Stadium in Syracuse New York, March 8-9, 1985. The film is just under two hours and features Rice students Regina Cavanaugh, Tanya McIntosh, Gawain Guy, Kattrice Harris, Tommy Welch and Monique Miller competing in various track and field events. Original resource is a color video.
    - 1987 NCAA Indoor / Practice 94-95, 198918
  - Track, Men's Basketball and Football, undated, 198872 (Box 148)
    - 2001-02 WAC Men's and Women's Basketball Video New Releases, 198916
    - 2001 Western Athletic Conference Men's and Women's Basketball Video News Releases, 198915
    - 80 Years of Rice Athletics (Men's Basketball), 198914
    - Men's Basketball vs. Northwestern Tape 1, 198913
    - Rice vs. Wyoming Sideline Tape 3 (Football), 198912
    - Rice vs. UT Basketball ESPN, 198911
    - Rice at San Jose (Men's Basketball), 198910
    - PIG (Men's Basketball), 198909
    - Men's Basketball at Tulsa, 198908
    - Men's Basketball vs. Florida St, 198907
    - Men's Basketball vs. Duquesne, 198906
    - Men's Basketball vs. Utah ESPN, 198905
    - Texas XC Relays (2 copies), 198904
    - Ivory Triple Jumps, 198903
    - Blank, 198902
    - Northwestern vs. Rice Continuous Endzone, 198901
    - Rice vs. Texas (Football), 198900
    - Rice vs. La Tech (, 198899
    - Colorado State Continuous Sideline, 198898
    - Northwestern Continuous Sideline, 198897
    - The Coach: Jess Neely's last game and interview, 1966; 198896
      These digitized video files consist of one master copy mp4 and one access copy available at scholarship.rice.edu. Color voiced film footage featuring 26 minutes of Rice University's football coach Jess Neely's last game and interview. Original resource is a color video.
    - Rice vs. Oklahoma (Football), 198895
    - UNLU vs. Rice Continuous Sideline, 198894
    - Rice vs. UTEP QB Club, 198893
    - 1st half Rice vs. Texas Tech, 198892
    - Colorado State vs. Rice Continuous Endzone, 198891
    - Utah QB Club, 198890
    - Rice vs. BYU QB Club, 198889
    - Rice vs. TCU QB Club, 198888
    - Run Test 8/15, 198887
    - UNLU vs. Rice Continuous Endzone, 198886
    - QB Club vs. New Mexico, 198885
    - Rice vs. Ohio State QB Club Highs, 198884
    - QB Club Highlights, 198883
    - Rice vs. Ohio State QB Club Highs, 198882
    - Truck Bay City, 198881
    - Kareem at U of H versus Carl Lewis, 198880
    - XC, 198879
    - Chris Jones – High school (Cross country), 198878
    - XC Camp, 198877
    - Track, 198876
    - Men's Track, 198875
    - Dave J 16'6''I (Cross Country), 198874
    - Football pics parade (CD), 198873
  - General Athletics; Bill Cousins, 198871 (Box 149)
    Formats: Cassettes, XBR
  - All Sports 1987-2006, 198870 (Box 150)
  - Unknown Beta tapes, CDS, MIIs, 198869 (Box 151)
  - Unknown Beta tapes, MIIs, 198868 (Box 152)
  - Unknown Beta tapes, MIIs, 1990s, SWC and WAC, 198867 (Box 153)
  - Unknown Beta tapes, MIIs, 198866 (Box 154)
- Series VI: Tickets and Autry Court flooring (Boxes 155-156), 198862
  - Unused tickets to Rice games of various sports, 198864 (Box 155)
  - Autry Court flooring pieces salvaged from 2007-2008 renovation, 198863 (Box 156)
- Series VII: Plaques by Sport, 1980s-2000s (Boxes 157-158), 198860
  - Plaques by Sport, 1980s-2000s, 198861 (Box 157-158)
- Series VIII: Addendum 1, 1940s-2000s (Boxes 159-166), 198850
  - Newsclippings, various sports, 1960s-1990s, 198859 (Box 159)
  - 16mm film reels of Track and Field events, Football including A&MFootball Fight, 1968 Olympic Games at Mexico City, Fed Hansen workout, 1950s-1980s and undated., 198858 (Box 160-161)
  - Rice basketball playbooks and programs, 1980s-2000s, 198857 (Box 162)
  - Rice football programs, 1960s-1990s, 198856 (Box 163)
  - Financial reports, all sports, 1982, 198855 (Box 163)
  - Baseball newsclippings (undated) and Football programs, rosters, 1940s-1990s, 198854 (Box 164)
  - Soccer correspondence, photographs and rosters, 1980s-1990s, 198853 (Box 165)
  - Football programs and scorecards, 1990s, 198852 (Box 165)
  - Rice Women's Athletics zipper bag, undated, 198851 (Box 166)
- Series IX: Addendum 2: 1950-2007 (Boxes 167-173), 198794
  - VHS Tapes of Women's Soccer Games, 2005-2006, 198849 (Box 167)
  - VHS Tapes of Women's Soccer Games, 2006-2007; also includes some DVDs, mini DVs, 198848 (Box 168)
  - Audio Cassettes of Football Games, 1985-1987, 198847 (Box 169)
  - Rice Athletics Photos: General, 198846 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Rice Baseball: Slides, 198845 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Rice Basketball: Photos and Negatives, 198844 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Rice Basketball: Slides, 198843 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Rice Owls Golf: Photos, 1929, 1966, 1986, 198842 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Rice Owls Football Photos: n.d., 1947-1967, 198841 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Rice Owls Football Photos: n.d., 198840 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Rice Owl Football Photos: negatives, n.d., 198839 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Rice Owl Football Photos: slides; folder 1 of 2, 198838 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Rice Owl Football Photos: slides; folder 2 of 2, 198837 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Rice Owl Swimming and Diving Photos (Men's and Women's), 198836 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Rice Owl Tennis: Photos, 198835 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Rice Owl Tennis Photos: Slides, 198834 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - Rice Owl Track and Field Photos: 1919-1928, n.d., 198833 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Rice Owl Women's Track and Field: Photos and Slides, 198832 (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - Rice Football Photos: 1951-1965; n.d., 198831 (Box 171, Folder -)
  - General Rice University Photos: slides, 198830 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - "R" Room Activities - photos, 198829 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Awards Presentation Photos, 198828 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Rice Staff Photos, 198827 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Rice Owl Volleyball Photos: Slides, 198826 (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - Rice Owls Football Photos: Large Negatives, 198825 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Rice Athletics All-Americans: Photos and bios (Photocopies), 198824 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Rice Athletics Hall of Fame: Photos and bios (Photocopies), 198823 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Distinguished "R" Man Awards: Photos and bios (Photocopies), 198822 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Honorary "R" Awards: Photos and bios (Photocopies), 198821 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Articles: A and M, 198820 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles: Arkansas, 198819 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Articles: Baylor, 198818 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles: SMU, 198817 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Articles: TCU, 198816 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Articles: Texas Tech, 198815 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Rice Athletics Newspaper Articles: 1986-1987 (copies), 198814 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Rice Athletics Newspaper Articles: 1987-1988 (copies), 198813 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Rice Athletics Newspaper Articles: 1988-1989 (copies), 198812 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - Rice Athletics Newspaper Articles: 1989-1990 (copies), 198811 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - Rice Athletics Newspaper Articles: 1990-1991(copies), 198810 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - Rice Athletics Newspaper Articles: 1991-1992 (copies), 198809 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - Rice Recruiting: Newspaper Articles, 198808 (Box 173, Folder 13)
  - Rice Athletics (general) Newspaper Articles, 198807 (Box 173, Folder 14)
  - Rice Athletics (general) Newspaper Articles: 1950-1951, 198806 (Box 173, Folder 15)
  - Rice Baseball: Newspaper Articles, 198805 (Box 173, Folder 16)
  - Rice Basketball: Newspaper Articles, 198804 (Box 173, Folder 17)
  - Rice Football: Newspaper Articles, 198803 (Box 173, Folder 18)
  - Rice Football Newspaper Articles: 1994, 198802 (Box 173, Folder 19)
  - Rice Football Newspaper Articles: 1950s (Opening of new stadium); folder 1 of 2, 198801 (Box 173, Folder 20)
  - Rice Football Newspaper Articles: 1950s (Opening of new stadium); folder 2 of 2, 198800 (Box 173, Folder 21)
  - Newspapers dedicated to Rice's New Stadium, 198799 (Box 173, Folder 22)
  - Rice Football: '91 Football Stories (games: TCU and Baylor), 198798 (Box 173, Folder 23)
  - Rice Football: '91 Football Stories (games: Texas), 198797 (Box 173, Folder 24)
  - Rice Tennis: Newspaper Articles, 198796 (Box 173, Folder 25)
  - Rice Track: Newspaper Articles, 198795 (Box 173, Folder 26)
- Series X: Addendum 3: 1920-2006 (Boxes 174-176), 198742
  - Rice Baseball: Individual athlete portraits, 1969, 198793 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Rice Basketball: Individual athlete portraits, 1968-69, 198792 (Box 174, Folder 2)